Flutter Developer

Uzbekistan / Toshkent

Mansur Gulomov

+998 99 941-58-35





WebSite in



LinkedIn



About Myself And My Brief Thoughts

I was born on the 24Th of may in 2000 in the Bagot region of Khorezm province. In the first period of the University, since 2019, I have entered almost all areas of IT and the most attractive one for me was mobile. I started to learn Android(java) in 2020. In 2021, I won unicorn grand of PDP academy and now I can write apps not only on Android but also on los with Flutter. I think that there are no complex things . In my opinion, everything is consist of typical things.

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Dart, Java, Swift, JavaScript, C++, C#.

TOOLS

Viual Studio Code, Android Studio, XCode, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Figma, Postman, Trello, Jira, Apple App Store, Google Play Store.

PLATFORMS

Apple, Windows, Android, Google Cloud Platform (GCP), Node.

FRAMEWORKS

Flutter, ExpressJS, Jaguar.

BACKEND AS A SERVICES

Firebase, Microsoft Azure (TTS and STT).

FLUTTER AND DART

flutter_bloc, getx, provider, scoped_model, http, dio, retrofit, retrofit_generator, build_runner, json_ serializable, animations, flame, hive, jaguar, sembast, shared_preferences, yandex_mapkit, google_maps_ flutter, and other packages......., Isolates, Futures, Async, Await, MethodChannel(call native code), Game Development.

OOP

S.O.L.I.D (Object-Oriented Design), K.I.S.S (Design Principle).

LANGUAGES

Uzbek — Native, English — A2 — Elementary, Russian — A2 — Elementary.

EDUCATION

National University of Uzbekistan

2019 - 2021

Faculty of Mathematics Applied Mathematics and Informatics. In 2021, I took an academic leave.

PDP Academy 2021 - 2022

Student of Flutter Bootcamp, group B14. Youtube

WORK HISTORY

PDP Academy 2022 - 2022 / 6 month

Teacher Assistant. Youtube

Programs Created During The Course: Link Here

Team Lead. Play Store

East Telecom 2022 - 2023 / 6 month

Junior Flutter Developer at Neva Team.

Neva Play Store Neva App Store

InCorp 2022 october - until now

Middle Flutter Developer at inCorp.

MEBEL Play Store MEBEL App Store

WisdTalk Carvan

My Self

Android Developer Rus Tili Play Store

Game With Flutter

Super Mario Snake Game Bricks Game Flutter Bird

Flutter Package <u>fractal_card_scanner</u>

My Hobbies

Listening To Music, Sport, Traveling Alone, Teaching, Playing Dota 1, Game Development